worldprofitleadsource.com 2011-06-07

# Privacy Policy | Worldprofit.com

**Our Commitment to Protect Your Personal Information** Worldprofit has been helping  
businesses online since 1994, longer than any other online business support company. The reason we’re still here is clear: people like what we do for their business and bottom line!

This page summarizes the privacy policy and practices on the Worldprofit Inc., website at Worldprofit.com. Worldprofit Inc., is committed to providing our visitors with a website that respects their privacy. We do not automatically gather any personal information from you, such as your name, address, phone number or e-mail address. This information is only obtained if you supply it voluntarily, usually through contacting us by e-mail or registering in a secure portion of the site. 

**Personal Information Management**

When you visit Worldprofit.com, our web server automatically collects a limited amount of standard information essential to the operation and evaluation of this web site. This information includes: 

  * the date and time of your page request 
  * the IP address your computer is using to receive information 
  * the type and version of your browser 
  * the page from which you arrived at our site 

This information helps us assess our information services and is  
used only for this purpose. This information is not used to identify  
individuals who come to the web site. 

If you choose to provide your personal information in an e-mail to someone else, or by filling out a form with your personal information included and submitting it through our website, Worldprofit Inc., will use that information to respond to your message and to help provide you with the information you have requested.

The personal information you submit is secure once it reaches our servers. In transit between your computer and the server, however, it may not be secure. If you would prefer to raise a comment or question in person, please see Contact Information. 

**Cookies and Session Variables**

This website uses cookies and session variables. Cookies are small amounts of information that are distributed to web browsers to assist you when you return to this site or a specific area on the site. The cookie used here retains session information, or more specifically, the options selected to determine your itinerary or to keep track of the items you wish to purchase (session cookies remain active only until you close your browser). Worldprofit Inc., does not keep a database of information obtained from these cookies or session variables. 

**Online Transactions**

When you ask to purchase a product from this site, you will have to submit personally identifying information, such as your name, the name of your company or organization (where applicable), your shipping and billing address(es), your phone and fax numbers, your e-mail address, the item(s) you have purchased, your credit card preference, and your credit card number and expiry date. We require this information so that we can deliver the software or services you request and collect payment from you for the product. 

When you submit this information, it is stored in a secure server. The information collected is used to process and deliver your order and collect payment as well as inform your sponsoring dealer of your order. This information is not disclosed to any Third Party except to authorized employees of Worldprofit Inc., who need it to process your order and bill or as required by law. The contact information you provide may also be used to contact you in the future about your order. 

**Internet Connection Security**

All personal information that you provide during your on-line transaction (including your credit card information) is protected by Secure Socket Layer (SSL) Encryption. When your information is encrypted, it is scrambled and rendered unreadable to anyone else. 

**Security**

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, Worldprofit Inc., employs software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, or investigation of malicious attacks on our servers, no other attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits. 

**Links to Other Sites**

This website contains links to external sites. Worldprofit Inc., is not responsible for the content and the privacy practices of other websites, and we encourage you to examine each site’s privacy policy and disclaimers in order to make your own decisions regarding the accuracy, reliability and correctness of material and information found there. 

**Retention of Your Information**

Only information necessary for the operation of the website and the provision of requested materials or services to you is collected. The information is used only for the purpose it was collected or for a consistent purpose. For instance, you may be contacted regarding the Worldprofit Inc., website, specific areas of the website, or services purchased on the site for quality, improvement or evaluation purposes. The information is only retained for the length of time necessary to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected. 

**Contact Information**

For more information about the collection of your personal information, any of the policies described above or about our website in general, please contact: 

Worldprofit Inc.  
Telephone: (617) 800-0637.   
Mon – Fri: 9:00 AM – 4:00 pm MT.  
Edmonton, Alberta, Canada
